Welcome to part 4 of the First High Homebuyer series. Today we're going to be going over the loan process.
So now you're pre-approved and you haven't accepted all from a property that you want to move forward with.
Now it's time to apply for your mortgage.
After you apply for your mortgage, your lender will now set up an appraisal on the property that you want to buy.
Once the results come in and the bank is happy with the results, now they might have a few conditions that need to be met.
After all the conditions are met and they're happy with the appraisal,
you'll now get a clear to close commitment letter allowing you to fully finance the property you like.
After you apply for your mortgage, the bank will now set up an appraisal.
Once the results come back and the lender is happy with the results of the appraisal,
they might have a few more conditions that might have to be met.
But other than that, you'll now have a clear to close amendment letter now allowing you to purchase that property.
I'll go over the last steps in my next video.
If you'd like a free homebuyer guide or you see homeownership in the horizons for you for the next 6 months to 2 years,
contact me directly at 917-951-2142.